Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 6066
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
6066
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records.
5792785
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Collective bargaining; Civil service; Government employee unions; Teachers' unions; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions; Zack, Arnold; AFSCME --Archives; American Association of University Professors -- Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Association of Machinists --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Chemical Workers Union --Archives; International Union of Operating Engineers --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; National Association of Government Employees (U.S.) --Archives; New England Health Care Employees Union --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Office and Professional Employees International Union -- Archives; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; Service Employees International Union; Trans World Airlines --Archives; United Paperworkers International Union; United Parcel Service --Archives; United Steelworkers of America; University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association --Archives; Zeldes, Needle & Cooper --Archives
5792785
- Alexandria Manor/NEHCWU. Greater Bristol Visiting Nurse Association/CHCA. (Box 1)
  - Alexandria Manor/NEHCWU 1/19/96 AAA E. Hartford, CT (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ansonia Copper/USWA 6445 9/26-10/18 1996 Shelton, CT (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arlington School District/Education Assn. 6/13/95 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Gelatin/OPEIU 1295 6/11/96 AAA Boston (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bailey Corporation/UAW 10/15/96 Hampton Falls, NH (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barnstable County/NAGE/IBPO 12/4/95 Hyannis, MA (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Barnstable School Committee/Teachers Assn. 5/2/96 Hyannis, MA (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bechtel Construction/IUOE 877 2/96 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bellingham/AFSCME 93 1/16/96 Bellingham Town Hall (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bentley College/IUOE 877 12/9/96 AAA Boston (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Berkshire Gas/USWA 12/13/96 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Boston Gas/Local 12003 11/21/95 & 12/20/93 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Boston School Committee/BPSBCA 10/31/95 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Boston School Committee/Boston Teachers local 66 10/25/95 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boston University/UAW 11/8/96 folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Boston University/UAW folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Boston University/UAW folder 3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Boston University/UAW folder 4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Town of Boxford/Police Association 1/22/96 Boxford, Mass. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Brown University/SEIU 134 12/6/96 & 6/18/96 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Capital Cities ABC/NABET 16 1/24/96 & 3/14/96 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Capital Cities ABC/NABET Local 16 3/14/96 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Capital ABC/NABE 5/15/96 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Capital Cities ABC/NABET 16 12/12/96 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Capital City Press/GCIU 745 6/26/97 Berlin, VT (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Central Adams School District/Federation of Teachers 5/14/96 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Chapin & Bangs Co./United Steelworkers 8831 9/12/96 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CSEA/Field Staff Assn. 6/26/96 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Conway School Board/Education Support Personnel 3/6/96 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CWA Agency Fee Challengers 96/97 folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - CWA Challengers folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cytec/ICWU 1/5/96 TBD (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Darien, Town of/Darien Police Assn. 11/19/96 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Dover School Board/Office Personnel 10/5/95 Mediation (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Duxbury School Committee/AFSCME 93 5/8-10/96 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Emery Worldwide/Teamsters 251 12/21/95 AAA Boston (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Exeter/IBPO Local 624 Factfinding 4/30/96 Exeter, NH (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Farmington School Board/Teachers' Association 6/17/96 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - FDIC/NIEU 2/8-9/96 Milford, MA (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Frontier Group/Hospital Workers 767 2/15/96 & 3/20/96 TBD (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Greater Bridgeport Transit/ATU 4/15/96 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Greater Bristol Visiting Nurse Assn./CHCA 4/16/96 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Greenburgh #11 UFSD/ NYSUT - Overseas Federation of Teachers. (Box 2)
  - Greenburg #11 UFSD/NUSUT 11/8/96 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Greenburgh/NYSU 5/7/96 AAA White Plains, NY (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Greenburgh School District/Federation of Teachers 1/10/96 White Plains, NY (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gorham School Board/Support Staff 5/1/96 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Groton, Town of/USWA 10/7/96 Groton, CT (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hampden Sheriff's Dept./IRI 11/7/96 TBD (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hampden County Sheriff Dept./IBCO 2/23/96 Ludlow, MA (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hollingsworth & Vose/UPIU 880 7/24/96 Leominster, MA (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hudson, Town of/Professional Management Association (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - IRS/NTEU 9/9/96 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - IRS/NTEU 9/20/96 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - IRS/NTEU 6/25/96 IRS Andover folder 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - IRS/NTEU 6/25/96 folder 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - James River Corp./UPIU Local 80 2/7/96 Bangor, ME (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kanzaki/UPIU 708 12/17/96 W. Springfield, MA (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Kanzaki Specialty Papers/UPIU 708 10/21/96 W. Springfield, MA (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Keene State/NEA-NH 11/25/96 Keene, NH (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Knights of Columbus/OPEIU 153 12/4/96 New Haven, CT (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Knights of Columbus/OPEIU 153 9/11/96 New Haven, CT (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lawrence & Memorial Hospital/Local 5049 10/17/96 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lincoln Greyhound Park/SEIU 334 11/15/96 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Litchfield 10/31/96 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Lynn, City of/AFSCME 93 5/21/96 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Lynn, City of/Lynn Police Assn. 6/4/96 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lynn, City of/Police Assn. 11/4/96 Lynn City Hall (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lucent Technologies/CWA 1365 6/14/96 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Macy's/RWDSU 12/19/96 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Madico/UE Local 262 4/3/96 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Manchester, City of/Police Assn. 4/17/96 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mass Electric/BUWNE 1/21/96 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - New England Pottery 12/18/95 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Optimum Care/NEHCEU 6/27/96 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Overseas Federation of Teachers 1/27-31/97 folder 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Overseas Federation of Teachers folder 2 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Oxbow/Union District 30 Board of Directors. Universtiy of New Hampshire/ AAUP. (Box 3)
  - Overseas Fed. Of Teachers folder 4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Fed. Of Teachers folder 5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Fed. Of Teachers folder 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Oxbow/Union District 30 Board of Directors 12/5/96 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Peabody School Committee/Federation of Teachers 3/28/96 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - City of Peabody/AFSCME 93 6/19/96 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers 6/10/96 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers 9/10/96 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - PondPoint/NEHCEU 5/13-8/8/96 AAA E. Hartford (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - President's Emergency Board 11/96 NMB (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Providence College/SEIU 6/12/96 Providence, RI (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Public Service Co./IBEW III 3/20/96 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Public Service Electric & Gas/IBEW 94 9/19/96 Mount Laurel, NJ folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Public Service Electric & Gas folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Public Service Gas & Electric/IBEW 94 6/13/96 AAA Somerset, NJ (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Rockland Community College/E. Padilla 5/24/96 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Scott Press/MLA Local 1 10/10/96 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - SEIU 1199/SEIU 6/6/96 folder1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - SEIU 1199/SEIU folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Shaws/UFCW 9/13/96 Braintree, MA (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Somerset School Board/Association of Educators 4/5/96 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Stone & Webster/IFPTE 5/22/96 AAA Boston, MA (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Temple University/NUHHCE, 1199C 1/8/96 AAA Philadelphia (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel 1995-1996 folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel 1995-1996 folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - TWA/IAM 6/20/96 Logan Hilton (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Union Leader Corp./Manchester News 1/14/96 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - University of Connecticut/Professional Employees Assn. 11/12/96 Storrs, CT (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - University of New Hampshire/AAUP (Box 3, Folder 29)
- UPS (United Parcel Service) /Teamsters local 776 - Zeldes, Needle & Cooper. (Box 4)
  - UPS/Teamsters Local 776 2/26/95-6/16/97 folder 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - UPS folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - UPS folder 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - UPS/Teamsters 776 Harrisburg, PA 9/24/96 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - UPS/Teamsters 6/3/96 St. Louis, MO (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Unite/FOUR 12/3/96 TBD (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Warwick/IAFF 2748 3/13/96 Warwick, RI (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - West Warwick/RI AFSCME 94 12/20/96 TBD (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Worcester/IAFF 1009 11/22/96 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yarmouth/NAGE 10/22/96 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Zeldes, Needle & Cooper 1/11-1/13/96 New Haven, CT (Box 4, Folder 11)